<resources>
    <string name="app_name">PokePlay</string>
    <!-- TITLE SCREEN -->
    <string name="start">TAP TO START</string>
    <string name="online">TEAM</string>
    <string name="options">OPTIONS</string>

    <string name="lesson_type1">Welcome to Type Dynamics.
        <br /><br />Here you will understand pokemon single and dual typing and how they affect a team. Pokemon moves also have types and here you will find out choosing attacking moves are not always straightforward.
        <br /><br />Let’s Get Started!</string>
    <string name="lesson_type2">The basic type practice involves is Grass, Water, and Fire. I simple two-way cycle, grass is super effective (SE) against water which is SE against fire and fire is SE against grass. There are 18 Pokemon typing and 171 type combinations, luckily you don’t have to remember all the interactions between them, only the basics and from there you can build and rationalize what Pokemon will have type advantage on the surface.</string>
    <string name="lesson_type3">Pokemon interactions with moves boil down to weaknesses and resistances. As mentioned, grass is SE against water, that means water has a 2X weakness to Grass. By pure design grass has a 2X resistance to water meaning it is not very effective (NE). NOT all typing interactions work so uniformly, and that is why knowing the basic single type interactions is both important and helpful. Type effectiveness are categorized into 4 labels; No effect (0), Not very effective (NE), Normal effective (1) and Super effective (SE).
    </string>
    <string name="lesson_type4">Values for NE and SE vary depending on dual typings of the Pokemon and certain status moves that cause Pokemon to gain new typings. Here you will learn up to dual typings which reach a max of 4X weakness and 4X resistances.</string>
    <string name="lesson_type5">The easiest and most convenient type interactions to remember are the No effect ones, because no matter the dual typing if this pokemon is hit with a move that has No effect on any of its both typings it will remain as No effect. Here are the No effect interactions: Ghost has no effect on Normal, Normal has no effect on Ghost, Psychic has no effect on Dark and Dragon has No effect on Fairy.</string>

    <string name="lesson_ability1">Welcome to Abilities. Pokemon Abilities have to power to change the tide of a battle all on their own. For that reason, players are particularly adamant about their Pokemon having the correct ability because most Pokemon have two or three abilities to choose from. Some abilities are useless in actual battle. Its important to know the effects these abilities have in battle because most abilities are not revealed to the opponent. Let’s Get Started!</string>
    <string name="lesson_ability2">Final stage evolutions, most often the strongest Pokemon in a certain evolution line, are the bread and butter of competitive Pokemon play and therefore we will concentrate on their abilities.</string> <string name="lesson_ability2_1">This is not to say middle stage or early stage Pokemon don’t see the light of day however some abilities become better or are replaced with better abilities once the Pokemon reaches their final stage. There are three types of abilities, passive, active, and reactive. Passive abilities show no on-screen interactions between Pokemon, while active abilities clearly state what their intentions are.
</string>
    <string name="lesson_ability3">Lastly reactive abilities activate once a certain condition is achieved on the battle field.Let’s get to know some examples of these types of abilities and how they change conditions on the battle field. Some abilities will help give your team a helping hand or will give your opponent a disadvantage.
</string>
    <string name="lesson_ability4">Steely Spirit is a passive ability because you don’t reveal it to your opponent. Steely Spirit gives you and your ally Pokemon a 1.5X boost to your steel type attacks. This makes steel type moves very strong, and if a steel type Pokemon uses a steel type move it get a Same Type Attack Bonus or S.T.A.B which increases the power of the move with an additional a 1.5X damage. This ability gives steel type moves a power boost to pour out the most damage while on the field.
</string>
    <string name="lesson_ability5">Intimidate is an active ability because it is revealed to the opponent and its effect is immediate. Intimidate lowers the attack of your opponents Pokemon by one stage (.66X) upon the Pokemon’s entry onto the field and the effect remains on the opposing Pokemon until THEY switch out.</string> <string name="lesson_ability5_1">Intimidate is one of the strongest abilities in competitive Pokemon because there is no clause in official gameplay that limits how many Pokemon with the intimidate ability you can bring or how many times you can switch out your intimidate Pokemon and bring it back to SPAM attack stat drops. Reducing damage taken is the other side of the coin because if you can’t boost damage the second-best strategy is to reduce damage you take.
</string>
    <string name="lesson_ability6">Competitive is a reactive ability because it activates only after your Pokemon’s stat is lowered. Intimidate may be very strong, but there are other abilities that check it. One of those is Competitive. </string><string name="lesson_ability6_1">If your Pokemon’s stats are lowered it will gain a two-stage boost to its Special attack and Speed. This is a great counter to Intimidate because the Pokemon with intimidate does not care about its physical attack stat drop and it can hit the opposing Pokemon harder on the special side while being much faster as soon as the Intimidate Pokemon lands on the field.
</string>


    <string name="team_builder">Team Builder</string>
    <string name="create_new_team">Create New Team</string>
    <string name="new_team">New Team</string>
    <string name="create">Create</string>
    <string name="select_pokemon">Select Pokemon</string>
    <string name="choose">Choose!</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
</resources>